<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>What is Hugo Catalog? on Hugo Catalog</title><link>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/</link><description>Recent content in What is Hugo Catalog? on Hugo Catalog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/installation/</guid><description>Prerequisites Hugo Installing Hugo Catalog is very easy, simply run the following command inside your themes folder:
git clone git@github.com:benmarte/hugo-catalog.git &amp;amp;&amp;amp; rm -rf ./hugo-catalog/.git Or simply download the theme and place it in your hugo theme directory.
How to customize and configure Hugo Catalog In order to customize your Hugo Catalog instance you need to copy the following code to your sites config.toml file:
theme = &amp;#39;hugo-catalog&amp;#39; [markup.goldmark.parser.attribute] block = true title = true [Params] # the path to your site logo logo = &amp;#39;/images/hugo-catalog-icon.</description></item><item><title>Shortcodes</title><link>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/shortcodes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/shortcodes/</guid><description>Audio Shortcode The Audio shortcode can be used to document the audible aspects, for example background music, sound effects or jingles in the browser-provided interface.
Shortcode Parameters
src: required string - the url pointing to the source file title: optional string - a title for the audio clip, otherwise the filename is used span: required number - [1–6] width of the shortcode autoplay: optional boolean - if true, the audio clip plays without interaction defaults to false muted: optional boolean - if true, the audio file will be muted default to false loop: optional boolean - if true, the audio clip plays repeatedly defaults to false HTML Example 6-second synth melody</description></item><item><title>Decap</title><link>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/decap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/decap/</guid><description>What is Decap? Decap is an open source What You See Is What You Get (WYSIWYG) that can be used with static site generators in order to provide an easy to use editor view while still taking advantage of using your CI/CD pipeline for deploying your site.
Prerequisites:
Netlify account Github OAuth app In order to enable decap you need to have a Netlify and Github account, if you don&amp;rsquo;t have an account sign up for a free one before getting started.</description></item><item><title>Logos</title><link>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/logos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/logos/</guid><description>Overview Feel free to download the individual Hugo Catalog logos or download the zip file which contains all logos.
Hugo Catalog Logo Horizontal
Hugo Catalog Logo Vertical
Hugo Catalog Icon
Hugo Catalog Logos 6.32 KB</description></item></channel></rss>