<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>What is Hugo Catalog? on Hugo Catalog</title><link>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/</link><description>Recent content in What is Hugo Catalog? on Hugo Catalog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/installation/</guid><description>Installing Hugo Catalog is very easy, simply clone the repo edit a few site settings and you are on your way to have your own brand style guide.
Prerequisites Before using Hugo Catalog you need to have either Docker or Hugo installed on your machine. Please refer to the installation links for these if you do not have them installed.
Docker Hugo How to run Hugo Catalog in Docker In terminal go the the directory where you cloned or downloaded Hugo Catalog and simply run:</description></item><item><title>Colors</title><link>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/colors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/colors/</guid><description>Overview Color is an instantly recognizable and important element of any brand. Applying our color palette will help create strong visual communication in everything from product UI to illustration and iconography.
Rewst Teal Rewst Purple is bold and vibrant. It is the only color weird enough to represent our creativity, wisdom, energy, and enthusiasm. It is our energetic brand expression building recognition in moments when our voice must be clear and memorable.</description></item><item><title>Shortcodes</title><link>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/shortcodes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/shortcodes/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Typography</title><link>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/typography/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/typography/</guid><description>Overview Typography plays a huge role at Rewst. It’s our vessel for us to speak both internally and externally. We rely on things like layout, color, and weight to create a hierarchy for our communications. Below you will find helpful guidelines around when, where, and how to use our approved typefaces.
Goldplay At Rewst we use Goldplay Sans for everything brand and marketing—from banner ads to billboards. Goldplay Sans is rounded, soft terminals give it a friendly and expressive look, and its modern and contemporary style as well as its classic proportions make it an excellent choice for headlines, logotypes, branding</description></item><item><title>Illustration</title><link>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/illustration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/illustration/</guid><description>Overview Rewst illustrations are a visually and emotionally powerful tool. Our illustration style builds off the simple shapes of our logo. Clean lines, intentional color, and playfulness are what give our illustration a branded feel and make them easy to digest and understand at a glance.
&amp;ldquo;Consistency speaks to quality: of the illustration and of the brand and products it represents.&amp;rdquo;
Tips Do Use illustration to help guide, explain, and add context.</description></item><item><title>Iconography</title><link>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/iconography/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/iconography/</guid><description>Overview Icons are a great way to signal, label, or highlight simple information with speed and clarity. At Rewst, we use icons across different brand touchpoints from marketing to environment to product. Below you will find 2 different libraries and guidelines around when to use each.
Streamline Icons In order to create a cohesive experience, we use Streamline Icons for all things Rewst Marketing. This library is beautiful and absolutely massive.</description></item><item><title>Decap</title><link>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/decap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/decap/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Hosting &amp; Deployment</title><link>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/hosting-and-deployment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/hosting-and-deployment/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Logos</title><link>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/logos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://benmarte.github.io/hugo-catalog-site/logos/</guid><description>Overview The Rewst logo is a sacred part of our brand. Because of that, it’s imperative that we protect it and use it correctly. To preserve the integrity of our identity, we want to ensure that our branding is always recognizable, legible, and stands out against any competing design elements.
Hugo Catalog Logos 6.32 KB Construction Rewst has been carefully constructed to provide personality and excellent visual clarity at all sizes.</description></item></channel></rss>